[{"answer": "Your so", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, sir, he is not", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "There wasn't one.  The police looked", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know.  I think so", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Snuff", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You know where I can get it?  I have a lot of money to spend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Twent", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't know, where are yours", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Where are your parents", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't mean any offense... but what are you doing mixed up in all this", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't know, where are yours", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm not mixed up in anything, hayseed.  What are you talking about", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What is this", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Her belongings", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Excellent", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "They should be here any minute", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Just tell me.  Tell me some more of the secrets you and that place shared. What kind of degenerate pervert was he really?  What the fuck did he want with a snuff film", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm asking", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I'm okay.  Please, honey, I can't explain.  Don't use the phone, just pack a bag and get out.  I'm on my way.  I'll be back at the house in three hours.  Call me from the hotel when you get ther", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Just do it, my friend, please, go", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You couldn't", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No, I don't, because you're not telling me anything", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What did you do, knock her out, shoot her up... ", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I want to know.  I want to know exactly what you did to her", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Tell me what happened", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Nobody saw you bring her in", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Do it", "docId": "8MM.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Do it!  Put me out of my misery so I don't have to listen to you whining anymore.  You think it's so easy", "qsentId": 28}]